(Inogashira Gorou)
Aobayama ... It's been about 20 years, huh
Wow~
A light Urasima Taro sensation
Has this town become like this?
Springy... Springy-boy
(NARRATOR) Time and society aside...
When hunger meets happiness
For a moment—
He becomes selfish and "free".
Unfettered by interference from others, he acts without concern.
The act of eating is a solitary one, an isolated activity that can only be truly experienced in the present moment
This act can be seen as the ultimate "healing" for modern people, who are often stressed and overwhelmed by their busy lives.
The best "healing" and
can be called
（Goro）
Is this place
Coffee and Fruit Shop
Is this also a Bunestyle...
（Staff）
Welcome
(Goro)
What's this mysterious spring?
(Kuroda(kuro-da)) Sorry to bother you.
(Goro) Ah, no, no.
Izumiji-san, if it's Western goods...
I asked someone to send anything over.
Yes, I cannot say "yes" to anything...
Is that so?
Who said that?
It was Mr. Takiyama
['Ah, Takiyama-san?
Ah, yes. I see.
(Gorou)
Takuyama...', 'Ah, the devil is fine, thank you.
Demon... is
E... Demon?
Yes
I collect western demon statues
Demon statue?
For example... Buzz!
Buzz?
(Kuroda) Amon ...
(Goro) Amon
(Kuroda) Amon is ---
(Goro) Yes
['(Kuroda) I spit fire out of my mouth.\n(Goro) Ah, yes.
(Kuroda) Do you understand?
(Goro) Yes, I do.
(Kuroda) What's it like?
['- There are two Puzzle and one each of Baphomet and Amon.
- Regardless of size, they can be carved from wood.
- Is that correct?
- (Kura) Yes, that's fine.
Well, I will contact you as soon as possible
Yes, please. Thank you
Ah, no, here I will...
(Kuroda) No, (Goro) No, let the customer--
You cannot afford to do that so
I am still here, so
Ah, yes. Then, please accept my apologies
(Kuroda)
Thank you very much
(Goro)\n
Ah
(Goro) Ahhh... That's a bummer...
Morning, I haven’t eaten yet, so my stomach is empty.
I feel like a clean slate.
Hmm...
(Gorou) Excuse me
(Shop clerk) Yes, please
(Shop clerk) Here you go
(Gorou) A glass of cold water, please
[Store Employee]
Here you are
[Goro]
Fruit sandwich
Maybe this is your first time...
It looks big
But it also looks delicious
Let's eat.
[Goro]
Oh
I thought that was different
Delicious!
Fruit sandwich
The feeling of fullness in the stomach is
refreshing than ever before.
Coffee becomes
more like a winna coffee.
Hmm
It’s good, isn’t it?
(Store Clerk)
Thank you very much
(Sigh)
Hika (Goro)
Thanks to the fruit sandwich
I feel refreshed
Okay 　Let's do one more job
Sorry.
Is your father here?
This is Inokozawa-san, right?
Ah, I apologize.
['Father, I've gone to my friend's place.
I have been away and haven't returned yet.
And you said, "If Mr. Inokozue comes, ask him to come over here."
Oh, is that so? Okay, but... where is it exactly...?
Sorry... umm... this is the right place, right?
I hope you can understand me. I don’t know if you can hear me clearly...
Hmm... I'm feeling a bit tired...
Oh, it's about 5-6 minutes from here.
Yes, sure. "You might as well get that too."
Oh yes.
Sorry, I’m being greedy now.
(Goro) Oh no, no...
（Gorō） Ah, no...
（Daughter） Oh, here it is...
（Daughter） Ah, and this...
（Gorō） Ah, yes...
It looks like it might rain...
Then...
Please --
Girou: As I step out into the arcade,
The townscape changes completely.
Wow, that's neat!
I find myself feeling a sense of familiarity in places like this --
Everywhere in front of the station is chaotic—
Maybe it's because it's too changeable
What is that chimney...
Huh, it's a municipal apartment
That's retro, huh?
Whoa? Did I go too far?
But this is heavy... What's inside?
Is this the place?
Oh dear, I've walked quite a bit, haven't I?
That guy... he didn't use it.
(Sound of customer conversation)
Um, Minaki-san...
Oh my god! Is it Hiroki?
(Gorou)
Oh yes
Sorry it was hot, wasn't it~
Come here, sit down
(Nami)
Oh, it doesn't matter.
I can't drink alcohol, you know?
(Nanuki) Really?
(Higasatani) Really?
Oh, really? That's a shame.
But you're still working, aren't you?
Oh, you're working too.
Ha ha…
You guys drank too much.
(laughter)
(Tomoharu): Excuse me?
(Takeshi):
Then?
(Mother): Orange juice
I also added柿ピー.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, this is from Lady…
Oh, I’m sorry.
(Minami) Here, I brought it.
(Higuchi) Oh, yes…
（Mom）
What is that?
（Nanuki）
Graduation album. Middle school and high school ones,
Ah- I want to see, I want to see,
（Nanuki）
Really?
（Gorō）
Uh?
Of course it’s heavy.
Oh - look... look look look
This is Masao from the photography studio.
（Higuchi）“Ah, yes.”
（Mama）“Oh?”
And this is me.”
(Mom)
Oh, Yoshio-san has changed too—
Southuki-kun...
(Mom) You don’t even look like yourself anymore
(Southuki) Ah~
He used to be cute back then
Ha ha ha...
(laughter)
(Mom) You've really changed, haven't you?
Mom,
How about Tomoaki?
Huh? Me? I'm here
You mean a guy like that?
Seriously?
Ha ha ha...
That's how it ended up like this
(Eto-yu) Sorry~
(Mama) Ha ha ha...
(laughter)
Oh…
This is the item you ordered.
Oh, I’m sorry.
By the way, also bad…
Could you bring this home for me?
You need to leave me alone! Take it back yourself.
Yes yes
It's such a tough job
(laughter)
It's not bad, you know
It's always like this
(Gorou)
Excuse me
Haa
(Gorou)
Work finished
I think it's because I walked a lot
I'm suddenly feeling hungry
Fruit Sandwiches are not filling
I want to eat something
That's right
I wonder if that store from the past is still open.
It was somewhere around here, wasn't it?
That's right, over there
Is it still warm?
Still the same as before.
Let's have another eel rice bowl
with ikura deep-fried in it.
Oh!
There's eel here too!
Umm
Let's do something new.
(Shop staff)
Welcome! What would you like?
(Housewife)
Excuse me, two chicken dumplings and...
(Gorō)
Oh! They also do grilled chicken here.
Wow! Eel! Eel!
On the unlucky days of *usshi* (the ox), it’s early—
My body craves eel right now
And this smell
(Store staff)
Welcome
(Gorō)
Excited by the smell of unagi for the first time in a while
His stomach grumbled loudly
Arrived safely
Ah
(Male floor staff)
Kindly let me know when you’ve decided.
I’ll call you.
（Gorou）
Fluttering bird…
Like a dish from French cuisine or something.
I never expected
To be able to meet with you at a鰻屋…
They also have tataki for sashimi.
Wow, he's setting up all kinds of schemes.
Oh no, without realizing it...
I was completely captivated by the fluttering birds.
Eel! Eel!
There it is!
So, let's order unadon.
Huh?
"Eel omelet"
(Gorou) Sorry.
(Male floor staff) Hai.
Are you ready?
Um
Plume birds assorted platter and—
Plume thorn skewers and plume fat thorn skewers
One each
Please give me a鰻 omelette
(Male floor staff)
Understood.
The 鰻 omelette will take a little time...
Is that okay?
(Gorō): Yes
Oh, and please a consommé as well.
(Male floor staff)
Yes, under your command.
(Gorō)
Just a little bit of ho-ro, I think I asked for too much.
(The Innkeeper) 2nd floor, three sets of unagi rice!\n(Kitchen) Okay!
(The innkeeper) Yes, please wash as well.
(The innkeeper)
It's finished, yes?
(Gorou)
It's really becoming a鰻屋.
(The innkeeper)
Yes~, please wait for the white sushi~
(Male customer) Yes yes, okay. There.
(Serving lady) Oh, excuse me
Okay
(Gorō)
Beer from noon, eel, the world of storytelling
This shop –
I bet I've been like this all along.
Oh!
(Male customer)
Yeah.
(Gorō)
Heh… This is nice.
Pardon the wait!
（Male floor staff）
This is garlic sauce.
Please enjoy!
Let's eat.
（Gorō）
Thick cut.
Looks delicious just by looking at it.
Well, this is a delightful first experience.
Wow.
Wow-wow.
This deliciousness.
“Encounter with the Unknown”
Good E.T. (Eee.T.)
This is the kind of guy who would just… linger.
Uhn.
With garlic oil…
Yeah, yeah
It's okay to hit
Hehe, hehe
Wow, that's absolutely right
This place is awesome!
(Gorou)
Wow, so many parts… Isn’t it delicious?
It’s really tasty~
One stick, a variety of textures
This is funny, isn't it?
Hooray!
This is also funny and good.
Ah
（五郎）
これは思わず声が出ちゃうよ
(Gorou)
Ah~
(Male customers) Ah~
(Gorou) Ah…
(Male customers) Ah Hah…
(Shop staff) Welcome
(Hostess) Welcome
(The Commander)
Yes, it's eel omelet.
Yes, I'll take care of it.
（Gorō）
It’s beautiful indeed.
It looks like you’re reluctant to eat it.
Oh~
Eel-kun emerges from the melted state…
Well, it'll be like this - sweet and fatty
Like an *unagi* restaurant with *yoshoku* vibes
Hmm... even if the *unagi* is inside the egg, it's still *unagi*
Friendly while also not losing yourself completely
Yeah…
Alright, let's go ahead and get some main eel rice bowls.
(Couple Man) Excuse me
(Gorou) Excuse me
(Male Floor Staff)
Please wait
(Male floor staff) Is that clear?
Two sets of premium unadon
(Gorou)
What... premium...
(Female couple) Is that okay?
(Male couple) Of course!
（Gorou）
You don't have to be so amazed.
(Male floor staff)
Is that everything?
Yes
(Male floor staff)
Is that an order?
Understood.
Incoming call sound.
Yeah, 'Kawae (Kagawa)' here.
Yes yes yeah yes.
(Male floor staff)
Unadon (rice bowl with unadon) is here.
I'll go down here
(Gorou)
That's fine. I'm good
(Sigh)
(Gorou)
Ugh ugh
It lives up to its name, unagi rice bowl
Delicious eel and white rice, the ultimate combination.
Shinjuku Line Stomach Pouch Rapid.
Why does the eel restaurant always serve plum vinegar?
I can't drink, and I don't really like plum vinegar... but this is good plum vinegar.
Oh, but this is good Nira-zuke
Delicious
But...
I'm getting a little tipsy
Ah
(Gorou)
That's good, that's good
Still eating, still delicious
The brilliance of the fluttering heroism fades away
Urn bowl sumo wrestling
Yeah
(sound of swallowing food)
(Goro)
This deep flavor
can't be made in one day or two
（Gorou）
Yeah.
(Gorou)
I've consumed history.
It was delicious.
(Staff)
Thank you very much.
（Gorou）
Oops…
Did I get drunk on Nara-zuke?
A big man getting drunk on Nara-zuke…
I’ll be laughed at by fluttering birds
Thank you very much
♪～
(Gorou)
Ah
Gotta go for an umbrella turn,
Let's go
~♪
(Narrator)
Original author Kazumi Masayuki—
Actual store visit
This will be the 67th year since the establishment of Akabana's ‘Kawae-Eri’,
We've been offering eel and poultry since our founding.
Now, as always,
Mr. Kuzumi just casually showed up.
Here, I'm stumped, but this…
With eel, ‘Upper,’ ‘Premium Upper,’ ‘Ultimate Upper’…
like that…
(Narrator)
Kusumi-san
ordered the three items you see
And…
(Waitress)
Small draft beer, one please?
Hi hi!
I wonder if a lot of people are drinking right now.
(Narrator)
By the way, it's 1:30 PM now.
Ah
（Narrator）
Let's start with the fluffy, succulent chicken skewers—
and the rose skewers have arrived, grilled to perfection.
The fluffy rose skewers feature 7 different cuts of meat on a single skewer—
A really special, limited-time item.
Let's start with the horobura kushi, one bite
(Kusumi)
Yeah, it's delicious
It's called 'abura' though...
It's incredibly refreshing and crisp...
（Narrator）
Continuing, delicious rose skewers.
(Hisayoshi)
This is tasty.
Really, lighter than chicken
because of the taste, you know.
This is easy to eat, isn't it?
Oh!
（Narrator）
Well, this *shinobe zume* ordered by Kusumi,
is where they hide the unagi beneath the rice—
that's why it's called *shinobe*,
It's a really extravagant item.
（Kizumi）
It's fine. Is this a sneak attack?
Sneak attack is under…
Got it.
(Kizumi)
This isn't a slippery slope...
(Narrator)
Well, slippery slope, how is it?
Oh!
(久住)
That's good
There seem to be many ways to eat this
Oh...
Hehe...
It's making me laugh.
(Narrator) I can't help but smile.
Please try ‘Kawae E” with everyone.